# Péter Bence Márföldi

Budapest, Hungary

☑ peter.marfoldi@gmail.com | 🌴 marfoldi.hu | 🖸 marfoldi | 🛅 marfoldi





# Summary.

Passionate engineer with an emphasis on writing clean, concise, idiomatic code. 8+ years experience specializing in full-stack development and consistently striving to work with my fellow peers make a meaningful impact. Interested learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

# **Experience**

### **Lufthansa Innovation Hub**

Budapest, Hungary (Remote) Feb. 2022 - Present

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Developing applications for partners in the travel industry.

**Ascenda Loyalty** Budapest, Hungary (Remote)

SOFTWARE ENGINEER • Implementing tools, services and pipelines to provide data to a booking and loyalty platform.

· Main contributor of a Reporting application that consumes data across multiple services and publishes results to our partners.

**BSSN Software (Merck Group)** 

Lambda-Com (WebEye Group)

Nov. 2015 - Feb. 2019 SOFTWARE ENGINEER

• Developing algorithms, services and CRUD applications to process scientific data.

• Interviewing/onboarding and supporting junior colleagues.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

· As a member of a scrum team taking part in the development of several web applications for vehicle tracking.

· Developing tools for data verification.

# Education

## **Eötvös Loránd University**

MSc in Computer Science Sept. 2015 - July. 2017

• Specialization in software technology (programming languages & distributed systems).

• Thesis title: Documenting functions automatically by recognizing stereotypes.

**Eötvös Loránd University** 

• Specialization in software development.

• Thesis title: A visualization and benchmark tool for sorting algorithms.

**BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE** 

Skills Languages Ruby, JavaScript, Java, C++

**Back-end** Hanami, Rails, Sinatra, Spring Front-end Vue.js, AngularJS, JQuery, HTML5, CSS, JavaFX, Swing

**DBs** SQL (Postgres), MongoDB

**DevOps** AWS, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes

Budapest, Hungary

Budapest, Hungary

Feb. 2019 - Feb. 2022

Budapest, Hungary

Jun. 2014 - Nov. 2015

Budapest, Hungary (Remote)

Sept. 2012 - July. 2015